DAVID RODRIGUEZ

MATHEMATICIAN



04/04/1994



dlrlima1994@gmail.com



+34 644587587

Portfolio: davewebportfolio.netlify.app

ABOUT ME

I am a dedicated and experienced university mathematics professor. I was also a researcher involved in a project called 'Biometric Cryptosystems for Post-Quantum Technologies', focused on developing efficient post-quantum cryptography algorithms implemented in C. I am currently learning and working as a web developer.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Professor

University of Informatics Sciences, Havana, Cuba | 2018 - 2019

- Logic, Discrete Mathematics, Algebra, Calculus teacher.
- Directed university student projects and forums in mathematics and computer science.

Professor/Researcher

Polytechnic University of Catalonia, Barcelona, Spain | 2021 - 2024

- Research on Cryptography, Biometrics.
- Significant contributions in the creation and optimization of a biometric cryptosystem for post-quantum technologies.

Self-Employed

2023 - Actuality

• Creation of websites for small businesses.

EDUCATION

University of Havana, Cuba

Bachelor's Degree in Mathematics | 2013 - 2018

University of Granada, Spain

Master's Degree in Mathematics | 2019 - 2020

SKILLS

- · Advanced mathematical thinking.
- C, Python, HTML, CSS, Javascript.
- React, Django, Bootstrap.

LANGUAGES

Inglish